http://www.artscatalyst.org/content/arts-catalyst-privacy-policy

Arts Catalyst Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).  We only use your information as set out below.We do not share your information with anybody else.Our websiteWe use web analytics technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our website. This includes using a "cookie" which is stored on your browser. If you want to, you can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening.Our email listIf you choose to sign up to our mailing list, we will use your personal information to keep you informed about events, news and offers that we think will be of interest to you. The type of information we will collect about you includes: Your nameYour addressYour email addressWe do track click-through links in emails sent as part of our e-bulletin subscription service. We do this to help us improve our marketing strategies.By disclosing your personal information to us using this website or our mailing list, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by The Arts Catalyst in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should email us admin@artscatalyst.org
About
People
Press
Opportunities
FAQs
Partners
Corporate Workshops and Away Days
